lushstories.com 2018-12-27

# Lush Stories Privacy Policy

## Contents

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How You Can Access or Update Your Information
  * The Way We Use Information
  * Our use of Cookies
  * Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Lushstories.com take your privacy very seriously. We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or other companies under any circumstances. By using or accessing Lushstories, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### The Information We Collect

When you register for an account with Lushstories.com, the only personal information we require is a valid email account for verification purposes, as well as your gender. Anything else you submit in your biography area is voluntary. You may delete your account or any information at any time. 

### How You Can Access or Update Your Information

You can access all your personal information in your profile area. 

### The Way We Use Information

The information you provide makes up the basis of your user profile at Lushstories.com. 

Your email address is only used for administrative purposes, to advise you of important site announcements, and to inform you of private messages from other members (should you choose to activate that option in your profile area). 

### Our use of Cookies

HTTP cookies are used by our web server to differentiate users and to maintain data related to the user during navigation, across multiple visits. Cookies allow our server to know that the user is already authenticated, and therefore is allowed to access services or perform operations that are restricted to logged-in users. The cookies are also used for personalization based on users' preferences. 

### Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use our contact page.
